你把好人送进了监狱
You put a good man in jail.
是你把好人送进了监狱
埃尔文·奥林斯基把他的命
Alvin Olinsky has dedicated his life
都献给了这座城市的人
to the people of this city.
他是把命给了你
He dedicated his life to you.
这才是他入狱的原因
That's why he's in jail.
你想怎么说随你  但你做事不地道
You say what you want, but you did him dirty.
我只是做了该做的事
I did him the way I had to.
坐吧
Take a seat.
我们把这事解决一下
Let's get this done.
我和汉克·博伊特警长在一起讨论...
I'm with Serant Hank Voight to discuss--
不要录音  我们达成一致之前不要录
No recordings, not until we have a deal.
好
Okay.
你说吧
Tell me what you have to say.
不录音的情况下你想达到什么目的
What kind of deal you looking for, off the record?
然后我们再具体讨论
We'll go from there.
就先假设
Let's say, hypothetically...
我坦白那个杀了我儿子的混蛋是我杀的
I confess to killing the son of a bitch who murdered my son.
我告诉你我追杀凯文·宾汉姆
I tell you I hunted Kevin Bingham like a dog,
让他自掘坟墓
made him dig his own grave,
然后一枪结果了他
and then shot him in the face.
把这话录下来的话
I say that on the record.
能够撤销所有对奥林斯基的指控吗
Would that be enough to drop all charges against Olinsky?
我觉得可以
I think it would.
我打电话给奥沙
Let me call Osha,
我们今晚就把细节全讲清楚
and we will work out all the details in person tonight.
我会听取你的话  汉克
I'll listen to your proffer, Hank.
如果你说的和丹尼在电话里
If everything you have to say is consistent with what Denny
和我说的一致  我就撤销
told me over the phone, I'll drop any and all charges
所有针对奥林斯基警探的指控  好吗
against Detective Olinsky, all right?
然后埃尔文明天一早
And Alvin gets released from Cook County
-就能被放出库克郡吗  -当然
- first thing in the morning? - Absolutely.
成交
Deal.
好
Okay.
我是助理州检察官詹姆斯·奥沙
This is Assistant State's Attorney James Osha.
我和丹尼·伍兹长官
I'm here with Lieutenant Denny Woods,
独立审计师
independent auditor,
以及情报局局长汉克·博伊特警长在一起
and Sergeant Hank Voight, head of intelligence.
我们讨论的事件是
We're here to discuss the events surrounding
凯文·宾汉姆谋杀案
the murder of Kevin Bingham.
和我们说说怎么回事  博伊特警长
Just tell us what happened, Sergeant Voight.
越详细越好
More details, the better.
你准备好了随时可以开始  汉克
Ready when you are, Hank.
汉克
Hank.
你好  我找埃尔文·奥林斯基警探...
Hey, man, listen, I'm looking for Detective Alvin Olinsky--
埃尔
Hey, Al!
芝加哥警署的  埃尔
Chicago PD. Al.
埃尔  是我
Al, it's me.
你要坚持住  听到了吗
You be strong, you hear me?
坚持住  埃尔
You hang in there, Al.
我没事的
I got this, man.
-我可以的  -我知道
- I got this. - I know, I know.
他们会治好你的
They're gonna fix you up.
你会没事的
You're gonna be-- you're gonna be okay.
医生  我是博伊特警长
Oh, hey, Doc. I'm Sergeant Voight.
-请问需要什么帮助  -那里面的病人
- How can I help you? - This patient in there,
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
奥林斯基警探  他怎么样了
Detective Olinksy, how is he?
他没能挺过来  我很抱歉
He didn't make it. I'm very sorry.
翻译     小酸奶   西之   不高兴童鞋   小萝莉
翻译     Lynn_宁   H小欠   风城章鱼X   圈圈
校对     圈圈
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
后期     8T
总监     圈圈
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第二十二集
你还好吗
You okay?
好
All right.
好吧
我知道
I know.
我们都很痛苦  我明白
I mean, we're all in pain. I get it.
但纪念埃尔的最好办法
But the best way to honor Al
就是找到那个要为此负责的混蛋
is to find the son of a bitch responsible for this.
所以现在
So, for now,
我们要把对埃尔的所有的力量
let's pull all our energy,
所有的激情和爱
all our passion-- our love for Al--
投入到找到那个混蛋这件事上
into finding the person who did this.
我知道那才是埃尔想看到的
I know that's what Al would want.
我保证
I guarantee it.
然后
Then,
当这事结束之后
when this is over,
当我们把这根刺拔了之后
when we got this prick,
我们才能缅怀埃尔
then we'll mourn Al.
所以
So...
给自己一点时间
take the time you need.
但要记住
But just know--
现在我们还有未完成的事
right now we got some business to do.
你真有胆子  还敢来这里
Oh, man, you got some balls showing up here.
他怎么样
How's he doing?
他死了  吉米
He's dead, Jimmy.
死了
Dead.
我认识埃尔二十年了
I've known Al for 20 years.
你亲手埋葬了他  我在场
Well, you buried him, and I was there.
-我当时在法院  -不不不
- I was in the courtroom. - No, no, no.
不是这样的
That's not how it went down.
-是吗  -我无能为力
- Oh, yeah? - My hands were tied.
牵扯了太多人
Too many people involved--
丹尼  州检察官  市长
Denny, the State's Attorney, the mayor.
那不代表你能...
That doesn't mean you just--
碾过他  把他埋了
just roll over and bury the guy.
-我是在尽我的职责  -你毁了他  吉米
- I was doing my job. - You screwed him, Jimmy!
汉克  听我说
Hank, listen to me.
别走  汉克  我别无选择
Stop, Hank. I didn't have a choice.
我知道你很有压力
I understand the press is all over you,
但是我在查清全部真相之前
but I'm not gonna give a quote or a statement
不会给你什么评论或声明
until I know the damn facts.
在此之前  所有电话都一概这么处理
Until then, just-- just refer all calls.
一概...你干什么
Refer-- what the hell you doing?
我要所有的监控录像
I want every piece of surveillance footage.
-汉克  也许我们能...  -我要找每个警卫
- Hank, maybe we could-- - I wanna talk to every guard--
-汉克  慢点  -和每个犯人问话
- Hank, slow down. - And inmate in the vicinity.
我是这里的典狱长
I am the warden of this place.
你以为你在和谁说话
Who the hell do you think you're talking to?
一个纵容某些混蛋杀了我最好的朋友
The son of a bitch who let some punk
埃尔文·奥林斯基的混蛋
kill my good friend, Alvin Olinsky.
我们会查出是谁干的
We will find out who did this--
我会查出是谁干的
I will find out who did this!
这是我的案子
This is my case.
你明白吗
You understand?
-我真是令人难以置信  -一
- You're unbelievable. - One,
我需要一间办公室  就设在监狱里
I need an office here, in the jail.
二  我要你在接下来十分钟内取得的
Two, I want every piece of evidence you have
所有证据
in the next ten minutes,
不然你和我可是有大问题了
or, you and me, we're gonna have a problem.
-现在什么情况  -监狱封锁了
- All right, where we at? - The jail is on lockdown.
好的  有情况随时通知我
Good, keep me in the loop.
警卫在搜索监狱  走廊
Guards are going through cells, hallways,
洗衣房有没有血迹
laundry rooms, looking for blood.
-有目击证人吗  -还没找到
- Any eyewitnesses? - Not yet.
我们找离刺伤地点很近的犯人问过了
We talked to inmates that were in proximity to the stabbing.
犯人都是瞎子  我明白
Well, inmates being blind, I get.
-警卫呢  -目前还没有收获
- What about guards? - No luck so far.
凶器送去分析了
The weapon's at the lab.
他们在查指纹和DNA
They're checking it for prints and DNA.
本来是一把塑料梳子  被改成一把小刀
It was a plastic comb before they turned it into a shank.
老大  我找到一名目睹袭击发生的警卫
Boss, I found a guard who actually saw the attack.
他叫迪兹  他在走廊等你
His name is Dietz. He's waiting in the hallway.
金  海莉  逐帧查看
Kim, Hailey-- track down every frame
手头上所有监控录像
of surveillance video you can get your hands on.
-明白  -收到
- Got it. - Copy.
我们当时正在护送犯人吃完晚餐回监狱
We were escorting the inmates to the cells after dinner
有人袭击了他
and someone attacked him.
有人  你没看到他的脸吗
Someone? You didn't see his face?
没有  发生得太快了
No, it happened real fast.
边上没有其他犯人吗
Were there no inmates standing nearby?
不  我就早点把他带回来了  想保护他
No, I brought him back early to protect him.
然后我手机响了  我就去接了
Then my cell phone rang. I got distracted.
等我转过头来  就看到奥林斯基倒在这边的地上
When I turned around, I saw Olinsky on the floor over here.
好了  等下再打扫
All right, finish up later.
我冲向他  叫人帮忙
I ran over to him, called for help.
-嗯  -我想止住他的出血
- Right. - I tried to stop the bleeding.
-你不知道是谁干的吗  -我说了  我没看到
- You got no idea who did this? - Like I said, I didn't see it.
要我说的话  我觉得肯定
If I were a betting man, I'd say it had something
和两天前的事有关系
to do with what happened two days ago.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
奥林斯基狠狠教训了个白人混蛋
Olinsky tuned up some Aryan Nation idiot real good.
把他的头往墙上撞了三四次
Slammed his head into a cell three, four times.
这个白人混蛋叫什么
All right, what's this Aryan prick's name?
-感觉怎么样  罗斯  -什么怎么样
- So how'd it go down, Ross? - How'd what go down?
捅人
The stabbing.
因为我们知道他可是好好修理了你一顿
'Cause we know he smacked you around like a little bitch.
你和你的小弟们决定让他尝尝苦头
You and your boys decided to get a little payback.
不是我干的  是我就好了
Wasn't me. Wish it was, though.
在这种地方干掉一个警察可是能树立不少威信
Taking out a cop has a lot of cachet in a place like this.
就像干掉一个恋童癖者或强奸犯
It's like taking out a pedophile or a rapist.
-是吗  -没错
- Yeah? - Yeah.
可惜有人抢先一步干掉了他
Too bad someone got to him first.
如果不是你  那是谁
Well, if it wasn't you, who was it?
去死吧
Go to hell.
-我要一个名字  -不知道名字
- I want a name. - Don't got a name.
只知道肤色...
Just a race...
捅你的人的是个...
Dude that stabbed your boy...
墨西哥的
was a taco-head.
搞到监控录像了吗
We get that surveillance video yet?
鲁塞克正在调出来
Ruzek's pulling it up right now.
四台摄像头  都是G区的
All right, four cameras, all of cell block G.
老埃从这边走出来
Here comes Al walking right there.
走向这两个人  他们开始挑衅
Walks up to these two guys. They start jawing.
警卫来了  制止了  这两个人继续走
Guard comes, breaks it up, two guys keep moving.
这是另一个角度  不同的摄像头
Now it's a different angle, different camera.
你看这个时候狱警还和他在一起
You're gonna see the guard still with him at this point.
然后这个地方狱警接到了电话
Now, the guard's gonna get a phone call
和他分开了
right here and break away.
埃尔继续超他的牢房走
Al keeps walking towards his cell.
事情是在这里发生的
This is where it happens.
播吧
Okay, run it.
等等  暂停
Wait, freeze it.
放大
All right, blow it up.
还是看不见那个混蛋的脸
Still can't see the bastard's face.
还有别的角度
All right, so we got any other angles?
别的摄像头吗
Other cameras?
调出来
Pull it up right now.
他在干什么
The hell is he doing?
-他就只是站在那里  -他是个懦夫
- He's just standing there. - He's a coward.
这个混蛋也参与其中
The son of a bitch is in on it.
这个人叫丹·迪兹
All right, his name is Dan Dietz.
查查他的账户明细  安东尼奥  走
Run his financials. Antonio, come on.
咱俩一起
You and me.
是谁收买你让你装没看到的
Who paid you to look the other way?
我们看到监控了
We watched the video.
那五秒钟里你就站在那里什么也没干
You just stood there doing nothing for five seconds.
-让我看看你的手机  -什么
- Let me see your phone. - Excuse me?
你根本没有接到电话  那只是场骗局
There never was a call. It was a scam.
埃尔发生的事和我没关系
Look, I had nothing to do with what happened to Al.
我们刚刚查了你的账户明细  蠢货
We just ran your financials, dumbass.
袭击发生的一小时前  有人往你账户里
Someone put five grand into your checking account
打了五千块钱进去
an hour before the attack.
你只有这一次机会来澄清自己
This is your one and only chance to come clean.
我...
I--
-快说  -好  我...
- Come on! - Okay, I--
我是收到了钱
I-I got some money.
可他说只是揍他一顿而已
But he said it was just gonna be a beatdown.
没说要捅他  我发誓
He didn't say anything about a stabbing, I swear to God.
谁  是谁收买了你
Who? Who paid you off?
谁
Who?
起来  我让你起来
Get up. I said, get up.
手放在前面
Hands in front.
放轻松
Take it easy, homes.
你因为谋杀警员而被逮捕了
You're under arrest for the murder of a police officer.
你跟我走
You're coming with me.
你买通的那个狱警  迪兹
The guard you paid off-- Dietz.
把你供了出来
He gave you up.
现在可能会有两种结局
This can go one of two ways.
惨
Bad...
或者是非常惨
Or really bad.
你坦白
You come clean.
告诉我你的原因  你的同伙
You tell me why you did it, who you working with.
坦白从宽抗拒从严
Things will go a lot better than if you don't.
去你的吧  你...
Kiss my Mexican ass, you--
好了  狱警  把门打开
All right, that's-- guard, unlock the door.
不用不用  没事没事
No, no, we're good, we're good.
听着  是这个人杀了埃尔
Listen, this is the guy that killed Al.
我知道  可是...
I know that, but this not--
你为什么想要保护他
No, what are you trying to protect him for?
站住  我们不需要你  不用过来
Stop, we don't need you! Stop!
退后  埃尔不会希望我们...
Back up. This is not what Al would wa--
我审问了那名囚犯
I interrogated the prisoner.
可他不配合
He was not cooperative.
我确定他牵涉其中
I am convinced he's involved.
天啊  汉克
For God's sakes, Hank.
他想用手铐勒死我
Hey, he tried to choke me with his handcuffs.
你到底在干什么
What the hell are you doing here?
你不相信我说的话
You don't believe my story?
-我想好好调查埃尔...  -我说了  他想用
- I wanna do right by Al-- - I said, he tried to choke me
手铐勒死我
with his handcuffs.
你不相信  那就投诉我啊
You don't believe me? Then file a beef.
然后别再插手这起案件调查
And get the hell off the case.
安德烈·戈麦斯绝对是我们要找的人
Andre Gomez is definitely our guy.
他的牢服和球鞋上都有很多血
There was ton of blood on his DOC uniform and his sneakers.
正被送去鉴定室
They're on the way to the lab right now.
安德烈·戈麦斯  35岁  惯犯
Andre Gomez, 35, long jacket.
与拉丁蝎有关联
Affiliated with the Latin Scorpions.
因为双重谋杀正在服刑
Doing time on a double murder.
对  他在库克县已经一个月了
Yeah, he's been at Cook County for a month.
案件正在上诉
His case is on appeal right now.
所以原因是什么
Okay, so why?
为什么安德烈要杀埃尔
Why Andre? Why Al?
他是警察
Well, he was a cop.
也许吧  可如果只是仇恨警察
Maybe, but if it's just police hate,
为什么要费这么多事
why put in all that effort?
这个人给了狱警五千块钱
I mean, this guy paid a guard
让他睁一只眼闭一只眼
five grand to look the other way.
我们知道这笔钱是哪来的吗
We know where this money came from?
从西联汇款转的账
Yeah, Western Union. It was a money transfer.
不过查不到转账人身份
We can't ID the sender, though.
这种判终身监禁的小混混
Right, so how the hell's some punk
怎么可能拿到五千块
doing life get his hands on 5K?
根本说不通
Doesn't make sense.
肯定监狱外头有人在帮他
Well, he definitely has somebody helping him on the outside.
问题在于究竟是外面的人在帮安德雷
The question is, is someone on the outside helping Andre,
还是安德雷在帮外面的人杀人
or is Andre helping someone on the outside?
你认为这可能是雇凶杀人
You think this could be a contracted hit?
我感觉像
Feels that way to me.
好  咱们深挖一下这个安德雷
All right, let's dig into this Andre.
看看他认不认识什么人
See if he's connected to someone
-和老埃有仇  -好
- who has a grudge against Al. - Yeah.
-金  -怎么了
- Hey, Kim? - Yeah?
等你准备好了  如果可以的话
Whenever you're ready, if you can,
你能不能拿个箱子  收拾下老埃的东西
will you get a box together? Get Al's stuff.
等你方便的时候  好吗
Whenever you're ready, okay?
奥林斯基的事可真是不得了
That was a hell of a thing, Olinsky.
那个傻子本来该在图森打九洞高尔夫
Dumb bastard could be playing nine holes in Tucson right now.
结果却躺在法医办公室的床板上
Instead, he's on a slab in the medical examiner's office.
这么忠心的人不常见了吧
Yeah, you just don't see that kind of loyalty anymore, huh?
这年头还没等你打招呼都有人会变脸
These days, most guys flip before you even say hello.
考虑到他今天的下场
Yeah, well, considering how things turned out,
他也许不该这么忠诚
maybe he should've been just a little bit less loyal.
那么现在怎么办
So what the hell happens now?
没了奥林斯基  我们该退一步
Without Olinsky, I think we should go back
针对博伊特立个案
and try to build a case against Voight.
咱们已经这么做了一整年了
Well, that's what we've been trying to do for the last year.
别激动好吗  丹尼
Relax, Denny, all right?
我只是说说我觉得下一步该怎么做
I'm just trying to tell you what I think our next move is.
我们有多少证据
So what do we have?
没多少
Not much.
现有的证据全都是间接的
All the evidence we have is circumstantial.
我还在追查  好吗
I'm just--I'm chasing it, all right?
我只是还需要一点时间想一想
I just need a little bit of time to think it through.
-我找到了个潜在证人  -证人
- I got a potential witness. - A witness?
一个女的  说她看见
Yeah, some lady says that she saw
宾汉姆和博伊特在杀人那天晚上在一起
Bingham and Voight together the night of the murder.
-而她过去这么久了才站出来  -是
- And she's coming forward now? - Mm-hmm.
为什么
How come?
我不知道  我还没和她谈过
I don't know. I haven't talked to her yet.
我明天就去见她
I'm gonna meet with her tomorrow.
你有这个证人的名字和号码吗
You got a name and number for this witness?
不行  不能这么做  我先和她谈
Nope, not a good idea. Let me talk to her first.
马上把她的名字和号码给我
I want her name and number now.
我当时在和宾汉姆约会
I was hanging out with Bingham, right?
我们在他家
We were at his house.
你们俩是恋爱关系吗
You two were in a relationship?
断断续续地谈吧
Here and there.
-关系也不深  -好  继续说
- It wasn't much. - Okay, keep going.
我和凯文刚刚抽嗨了
Me and Kevin were just getting stoned.
然后突然间有人踢门
And all of a sudden, someone kicks in the door.
然后有个警察进来抓住凯文的头发
Right, and this cop comes in, grabs Kevin by the hair,
把他拖出去了
and drags him outside.
你怎么知道是个警察
How do you know it was a cop?
我在新闻上看到了他的照片
So I saw his picture on the news.
他儿子没多久之前被人谋杀了
He's the one whose son got murdered a while back.
你看到的是这个人吗
Is this the man you saw?
就是他
That's him.
他叫博伊特
His name's Voight.
他把凯文拖出去之后怎么样了
So what happened after he dragged Kevin outside?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
我没看
I didn't look.
你怎么没早找警察报告这事
How come you didn't report this earlier?
因为我害怕
'Cause I was afraid.
那警察说如果我说出去就杀了我
That cop said if I opened my mouth, he'd kill me.
-你现在就不怕了  -我可没这么说
- But you're not afraid now? - I didn't say that.
我不明白
I'm confused.
好吧  是这样
All right, look.
事实就是
Truth is,
我差不多快把这事忘了
I sort of forgot about what happened.
我继续生活了
I moved on.
但是后来我在新闻上
But then, I saw on the news
看到他们为了凯文被杀的案子抓了别的警察
that they arrested some other cop for Kevin's murder.
让我想起了我看见的事
Reminded me of what I saw.
于是我就想着
It made me realize that
我手上的情报应该挺值钱
I was sitting on some pretty valuable information.
所以我觉着我应该找什么人谈谈
So I thought it made sense for me to talk to someone.
看看这情报有多值钱
You know, find out how much it may be worth.
事儿不是这么办的  明白吗
That is not how this works, all right?
这件事扯不到钱上
There's no money involved here.
这样啊  反正我破产了
Yeah, well, look, I'm broke.
也没工作  也没保险
I got no job. I got no insurance.
所以我并不是真的关心这事到底怎么样了
So I don't really care about any of that.
你想要我帮你  就给我两万块
If you want my help, price is 20 grand.
查到什么了吗
So, we got anything yet?
我们详细查了查老埃办过的旧案
We're doing a deep dive into Al's old cases.
迄今为止所有他逮捕过的人
Everyone he's ever arrested so far,
他们有一个共同点
they've got one thing in common.
没有什么和安德烈·戈麦斯的关联
There's no connection whatsoever to Andre Gomez.
那我们对于这个混混还知道什么
All right, so what else do we know about this punk?
警长  我们有发现了
Sarge, I think we got something.
上周在库克县安德烈有两位拜访者
Andre had two visitors last week at Cook County--
他母亲和他律师
his mother and his lawyer.
他律师是菲德尔·卡斯特罗
His lawyer's name is Fidel Castro.
很明显是化名
Obviously the name's bogus.
-好  面部识别呢  -还没结果
- Okay, facial rec? - Nothing yet.
关于这个人现在有线索吗
Well, we got any leads on this guy?
安德烈和菲德尔见面那天
Yeah, Andre made two phone calls
打了两通电话
the day he was meeting with Fidel,
那个号码的所有者是
and they were both to a cell phone
阿尔伯特·弗洛斯
registered to an Alberto Flores.
我去定位这号码
I'll work on getting it pinged.
你和安东尼奥去查  鲁塞克  你和我一起
Okay, you and Antonio. Ruzek, you ride with me.
继续查
Keeping digging.
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD!
阿尔伯特·弗洛斯
Alberto Flores!
不许动
Nope.
过来
Come here.
起来
Get up.
很好  就在这里审
All right, we're good. We got it from here.
你确定吗  我们可以带走他
You sure? We can take him.
不  我们可以搞定
Nah, we're good.
我做什么了  怎么了
Yo, what did I even do, man? What's going on?
你去安德烈·戈麦斯那儿探监了  对吧
You visited Andre Gomez in prison, right?
我都不知道那是谁
I don't even know who that is.
不不  这是谁
No? No? Who's this?
这是谁  是你吗  阿尔伯特
Who is this? Is that you, Alberto?
用菲德尔·卡斯特罗这名字登记的
Signed in under Fidel Castro?
你们说了什么
What'd you talk about?
-古巴  -古巴
- Cuba. - Cuba?
-你为谁工作  -不为谁
- Who you working for? - Nobody.
你不该这么回答
That's the wrong answer.
看着我
Hey, look at me.
你让安德烈·戈麦斯去杀人了吗
Did you tell Andre Gomez to kill someone?
是还是不是
Yes or no.
Yes or no?
是
Yeah.
你有同伙吗
Are you working with anyone else?
不不不  只有我一个
No, no, no, just me.
你就是个三流混混  阿尔伯特
You're a small-time punk, Alberto.
你没有五千块买通监狱看守
You don't have 5K to pay off a prison guard.
这意味着你撒谎了
That means you're lying.
那是第一棒  你的同伙是谁
That's strike one. Now, who you working with?
没人  只有我
No one, just me--
第二棒  再问一次
Strike two. One more.
我不能说  他会杀了我
I can't, he'll kill me.
-你以为我会怎么做  -不
- What do you think I'm gonna do? Huh? - No.
最后一次机会  阿尔伯特
Last chance, Alberto.
不  等等  我说  求你了
No, wait, wait, wait! Okay, okay! Please, please.
他是卡洛斯·利昂
His name is Carlos DeLeon, okay?
卡洛斯·利昂
Carlos DeLeon!
把他带走
Take him.
查到了  卡洛斯·利昂为卡利贩毒集团洗钱
Got him--Carlos DeLeon washes money for the Cali Cartel.
通过他名下的合法家具生意洗钱
Runs the cash through a legit furniture business that he owns.
联调局追踪他好几年了
The feds have been after him for years,
但这家伙简直是特氟龙做的  无懈可击
but this guy's made of Teflon.
-和奥林斯基有什么关联  -还没查到  警长
- Any connection to Olinsky? - Nothing yet, Sarge.
我刚和缉毒局的探员沟通了
I was just talking to an agent at the DEA.
老埃多年前参与了缉毒局的一个特遣部队
It turns out, Al got loaned out to a DEA task force years back.
-目标就是卡洛斯·利昂  -那是联邦案件
- The target was Carlos DeLeon. - It was a federal case.
所以我们资料里查不到
That's why it's not in our files.
他为什么对奥林斯基怀恨在心
So why the grudge against Olinsky?
他弟弟因为超速被捕
His little brother got popped for speeding.
他车里有一批抢
He had a load of guns in the car.
联调局把他关起来  想让他供出卡洛斯
The feds lock him up and try to give him the flip on Carlos.
这就是平常的套路
That sounds like business as usual.
是啊  直到他弟弟在监狱被杀
It was until little bro gets killed in jail.
所以老埃也在监狱被杀
So Al gets made in jail.
这事传到利昂那儿
Somehow, word gets back to DeLeon,
他就雇人报复老埃
and DeLeon orders a hit on Al to get revenge.
我们现在就去抓他
Let's grab this guy now.
行动
Hit it.
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD!
-你们要干嘛  -卡洛斯·利昂
- What do you want? - Carlos DeLeon!
-他不在这里  -他在哪里
- He's not here. - Where is he?
你们不能没搜查令就闯进来
You can't come in my house without a search warrant--
我们有   托马斯·威尔斯法官签署的
Right here, signed by Judge Thomas Wells.
你丈夫  卡洛斯  在哪
Well, your husband, Carlos-- where is he?
我告诉你了  他不在这里
I told you, he's not here.
在后面找到她的  警长
Hey, I just found her in the back, Sergeant.
不知道她是不是说英语
I don't know if she speaks English or not.
你的名字[西语]
What's your name? Tu nombre.
-苏珊娜  -闭嘴
- Susana. - Cállate!
她是我妈  把你的手拿开
She's my mother. Now get your hands off of her.
卧室地上的手提箱里
There's men's clothes in the suitcase
有男人的衣服
on the floor in the bedroom.
看来有人离开得很匆忙
Looks like someone left in a hurry.
他去哪了
All right, where'd he go?
墨西哥
Mexico?
我丈夫出差了
My husband travels for business.
他是卖家具的
He sells furniture.
你丈夫为毒贩洗钱
Your husband launders money for the cartel,
他下令谋杀了一位芝加哥警官
and he ordered the murder of a Chicago police officer.
所以你现在有机会和我们合作
So you got one chance to cooperate.
不然呢  你就打我吗
Or what? You gonna hit me?
警长  我们来吧
Sarge, we got this.
让海莉和我跟她聊聊
Let Hailey and I talk to her.
好主意
That's a good idea.
-把这地方翻个底朝天  -走
- Tear this place apart. - Come on.
-跟我走  -走
- Come with me. - Go.
好了  卡门  从你嫁给卡洛斯的那天起
Come on, Carmen, you knew the day
你就知道会有这么一天的
you married Carlos this moment was coming.
好好配合  你就没事  不配合的话  你...
Play it right, you walk, play it wrong, you--
我丈夫是卖家具的
My husband sells furniture.
现在给我滚开
Now get the hell out of my face.
你听我说  你个婊子
You listen to me, you bitch.
你丈夫杀了我的搭档  你明白吗
Your husband killed my partner. Do you understand?
要么你现在帮我
So either you help me here and now,
-要么老娘就宰了你  -我要打给我律师
- or I will bury your ass. - I'm calling my lawyer.
他们叫他"鲨鱼"
They call him "The Shark."
他会让你们生不如死的
He'll make your life a living hell.
打啊
Call him.
-她得留在这  -没她什么事
- She stays. - For God's sake, leave her alone.
我会的  我需要先看看她的证件
Oh, I will. I need her papers first.
她和这事无关
She has nothing to do with this.
-证件  -看这条讯息
- Papers now. - Look at this text.
好  我们查了你妈
Okay. We ran your mother's name.
似乎她并不存在
Seems she doesn't exist.
我想她是非法偷渡到这里的
I'm guessing she's here illegally.
给移民总署打个电话  她就被遣返了
One call to ICE and she's gone.
做慢车回墨西哥  卡门
Slow train back to Mexico, Carmen.
这真的是一个很简单的选择  你亲爱的妈妈...
It's a real easy choice-- your sweet, loving mother...
还是你要在监狱里度过余生的
Or your scumbag murdering husband.
人渣杀人犯丈夫
Who's going to prison for the rest of his life.
最后一次机会
Last chance.
他在哪
Where is he?
雷蒙大约一小时前把他接走了
Ramon picked him up about an hour ago.
-谁是雷蒙  -卡洛斯的表亲
- Who's Ramon? - Carlos' cousin.
-他们在他的仓库里  -很好
- They're at his warehouse. - There you go.
-如果你是撒谎...  -我没有
- If you're lying-- - I'm not.
走吧  做你们要做的事
So go. Do what you gotta do.
等等
Hold.
阿特沃特  安东尼奥和我一起
All right, Atwater, Antonio with me.
你们去右边  走吧
You guys go right. Let's move.
-行动  -上
- Go. - Moving.
你们准备好了吗  准备好了
You guys ready? Ready.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
在你后面
Behind you.
-走  伯吉斯  -好
- Let's go, Burgess. - Yep.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You good? - Yeah, I'm good.
他还活着  走吧
He's still alive. Go.
哪来的  哪里  哪里
Where'd it come from? Where, where, where?
上
Go.
警长  你看到什么了吗
Sarge, you see something?
你从那边走  我往这
You go that way. I'm going here.
-等等  我...  -这是命令
- Oh, wait, I was-- - It's an order.
卡洛斯·利昂
Carlos DeLeon.
别开枪  别开枪
Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
我没拿枪
I don't have a gun.
把包扔下
Drop the bag.
扔下
Drop it!
好  好  好  我没拿枪
Okay, okay, okay. I don't have a gun.
把手举到头顶
Get your hands above your head.
包里有40万  可能更多
Listen, there's 400 grand in that bag, maybe more.
-闭嘴  -你拿走就行
- Shut up. - Just take it.
-闭嘴  -没人知道的
- Shut up! - No one's gonna know.
拿走就好
Just take it.
把手举到头顶
Get your hands over your head!
求求你  别开枪
Please, don't shoot me.
埃尔文·奥林斯基是我最好的朋友
Alvin Olinsky was my best friend.
求求你  求求你
Please, please.
-跪下  -别开枪
- Get on your knees. - Don't shoot me.
-别开枪  -跪下
- Don't shoot me-- - Get on your knees!
汉克  你没事吧
Hank, you okay?
发生什么了
What happened?
他想拿他腰那里的枪
He's got a gun in his waistband he was reaching for.
怎么回事  你刚刚杀了他
Yo, what the hell, man? You just killed that dude!
他都把手举起来了  你还是开枪了
He had his hands up. You shot his ass anyway.
我都看到了  你冷血地杀了他
I saw the whole thing. You shot him in cold blood.
你没有这个权利  没有权利
You got no right to do that! No right at all!
外面怎么样
What happened out there?
那个目击者在新闻上
This witness is all over
到处说利昂的双手举得很高
the news saying DeLeon's hands were up high?
是的  他说的是实话吗
Yeah, is he telling the truth?
我不知道  我没看到
I don't know. I didn't see it.
我到现场时博伊特刚刚开完枪
I got to the scene right after Voight opened fire.
媒体都在疯狂报道这事
Press about to go crazy over this.
是的  这对博伊特来说可不是好事
Yeah, this is not a good look for Voight.
我知道  但是
I get it, but I mean--
但是什么
But what?
我也没办法  我不在场
There's nothing I can do. I wasn't there,
所以我不能确认或否认卡洛斯想拿武器
so I can't confirm or deny if Carlos reached for his weap--
你不能确认或否认  怎么  你是律师吗
You can't confirm or deny? What, are you a lawyer?
-我没看到事情经过  -这不重要
- I didn't see what happened. - It doesn't matter.
-谁关心啊  -什么
- Who cares? - Excuse me?
我们现在说的是杀了老埃的家伙
We're talking about the guy who killed Al here.
是那个惯犯付钱指使别的混蛋杀人
We're talking about a career criminal
杀了我们的朋友  我们的大哥
who paid some punk to kill our friend, our brother,
现在你还在想自己有没有看到什么
and you're worried about what you saw or didn't see?
-我就不明白了  -你小心点
- I don't understand. - Watch yourself.
-我小心点  我就在这  -好了  够了
- Watch myself? I'm right here. - All right, enough!
-现在别这样  -你们这是干什么
- Not today. - What is going on?
没事
We're good.
就是说点事情
We're just talking over a few things.
安东尼奥
Antonio,
上面打电话了来
Ivory Tower called.
他们想跟你谈卡洛斯·利昂被杀的事
They wanna talk to you about the Carlos DeLeon shooting.
现在
Now.
吉米·欧沙
追捕时
In the course of pursuit,
我设法把罪犯引到了仓库的屋顶
I managed to trap the offender on the roof of this warehouse.
我命令罪犯把双手举到头上
And I ordered the offender to raise his hands above his head,
跪到地上
get down on his knees.
他拒绝服从我的命令
He refused to comply with my order.
然后他的手伸向裤腰想拿枪
And he reached into his waistband for a handgun.
这时  我担心自己的生命
At this point, I was afraid for my life,
所以开了一枪  正中胸口
so I fired one shot, center mass.
罪犯倒下了
Offender went down.
然后在地上他又伸手想拿枪
And on the ground he reached again for his handgun,
所以我又朝他心脏开了致命的一枪
so I fired a second lethal round through his heart.
就是这样  事情的经过
And that's it. That's what happened.
还有什么要说的吗
Anything else you'd like to add?
那枪  那枪没开错
Yeah, it was-- it was a good shoot.
我只能这么做
I mean, I did what I had to do.
就这么简单
Simple as that.
你迟到了
You're late.
为什么三次换地点
Why'd you change the location three times?
别管这个  你的手机给我看看
Don't worry about it. Let me see your phone.
-什么  -我说  把你的破手机给我
- What? - I said, give me your damn phone.
为什么
Why?
我想看看你在跟谁聊天
I wanna see who you've been talking to.
现在项链拿下来  放到这个袋子里
Necklace, off, in this bag right now.
你干什么呢
The hell are you doing?
-小心为上  -这是不尊重人
- Just being cautious. - You mean disrespectful.
从你开始要钱  游戏规则就变了  宝贝
When you ask for money, the rules change, sweetie.
现在就是这样了
That's just the way it is.
你还有别的要检查吗
Anything else you wanna check?
不用了  没事了
Nah, we're good.
想拿钱  你得稍微
You want the money, you need to make
改一下你的证词
a few adjustments to your testimony.
你不仅只是看到博伊特和宾汉姆离开
You didn't just see Voight and Bingham leave the house.
你看见博伊特拿枪指着他的头
You saw Voight put a pistol to his head,
把他扔进后备箱
throw him in the trunk of the car,
说  "你对我儿子做的事是时候偿还了"
and say, "It's time for you to pay for what you did to my son."
-你想让我撒谎  -你想要两万块吗
- You want me to lie? - You want the 20 grand?
好的  行吧  你想让我说什么我就说什么
Yeah, sure, fine. I'll say whatever you want.
很好
All right, good.
明天一早我就安排你
I'll set up a meeting with the prosecutor
跟检察官见面
first thing in the morning.
你把跟我说的事全部告诉他们
You tell them exactly what you told me,
还有我们刚刚说过的新的细节
plus the new details we talked about.
好
Okay.
现在给你一万
You get 10 grand now,
作证之后再给你一万
10 grand after you testify.
好的  随你  可以
Yeah, whatever, man. That's cool.
祝你愉快
Yeah, have a nice day.
汉克  是我
Hank, it's me.
我们私下聊一下
We need to talk in private.
请进  喝什么
Come on in. Drink?
谢谢不用了
No thanks.
好吧
Okay.
那就算了
I'll cut to it.
我们有一个目击者  说谋杀案当晚
We have a witness that put you and Bingham together
看到你和宾汉姆在一起
the night of the murder.
那有可能是压倒
And it, uh, might just be the straw
汉克·博伊特的最后一根稻草
that breaks old Hank Voight's back.
我还是喝一杯酒吧
Maybe I will take one of those bourbons,
如果你还想请我喝
if you're still offering.
事情是怎么变成这样的
How'd things get so crazy,
你我之间的事
you and me?
我们曾经是搭档
Man, we were partners.
是朋友
Friends.
是你先对付我的
You came after me.
你让我别无选择
You left me no choice.
丹尼  你越界了
Denny, you crossed the line.
32年来就那么一次
What, once in 32 years?
丹尼
Denny...
你把一把枪栽赃给了一个无辜的人
You planted a gun on an innocent man.
这种事我不能忍
That's not something I can abide.
你不能忍
Not something you can abide?
你算老几
Just who the hell are you?
芝加哥最黑的警察来容忍
Dirtiest damn cop in Chicago to abide
或者不容忍我的行为
or not abide my actions.
我不是黑警
I'm not dirty.
我不伤害无辜的人
I don't hurt innocent people.
我从来没有  以后也不会
I never did. I never will.
你这是开完笑吗
Is that a joke?
你就是不懂  对不对
You don't get it, do you?
都这么久了
After all this time.
懂什么
Get what?
黑和必要之间的区别
The difference between dirty and necessary.
不管你喜不喜欢
That, like it or not,
你和你那些以正人君子自居的高层朋友
you and all your self-righteous friends in the Ivory Tower,
你们需要我这样的人在街头
you need people like me out on the streets,
做普通警察不愿做的事
doing the things regular cops are unwilling to do,
多花点心思
going the extra mile
确保真正的恶人
to make sure the truly evil,
真正危险的人
the truly dangerous,
远离芝加哥
go away.
我是为了人民惩奸除恶
I thin the herd for the greater good.
我也惩奸除恶
Well, I thin the herd, too,
处理掉不规矩的警察
getting rid of cowboy cops.
我只想确保芝加哥的生活环境更美好
I just want to make Chicago a better place to live.
不
No.
你根本不在乎芝加哥
You don't give a damn about Chicago.
你从没在乎过
You never did.
你只在乎你自己  丹尼·伍兹
You care about you, Denny Woods.
这件事从头到尾都是
That's what this is really about...
关于你
You...
还有你的自尊  你的野心
your ego, your ambition.
有件事特别疯狂你知道吗
You know what's crazy?
尽管发生了那么多事
I mean, despite all that's happened...
我还是爱你  汉克
I still love you, Hank.
我也不知道为什么  我就是爱你
Damn if I know why, but I do.
所以我才愿意跟你打成协议
That's why I am willing to offer you a deal.
你承认杀害宾汉姆
Now, you confess to killing Bingham,
我们会辩护为过失杀人
we'll plead you down to manslaughter.
你会在监狱待个五年  最多七年
You'll do five years, maybe seven.
跟我说说你找到的那个证人
Tell me about this witness you found.
你知道我不能说
Aw, now you know I cannot do that.
她可信吗
Is she credible?
"她"
"She"?
她叫凯特  是吧
Name's Kate, right?
你给了她两万  先给一万  事后再给一万
You gave her 20 grand-10 now, 10 later?
贿赂证人
Bribing a witness...
这可是重罪
That's a serious crime.
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
你让我别无选择
You left me no choice.
我只能把带子交给内务部
I had to give that tape to Internal Affairs.
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD!
结束了  丹尼
It's over, Denny.
先生  我需要你站起来
Sir, I'm gonna need you to stand up.
请交出你的枪和警徽
I'm gonna need your gun and your badge.
你成功了
You pulled it off.
嗯  他死路一条了
Yeah, he couldn't help himself.
那个混蛋是自作自受
Son of a bitch had it coming.
听着  谢谢你这么做  吉米
Listen, I appreciate what you did, Jimmy.
也谢谢你  凯特
You too, Kate.
埃尔的事我说的是真心的
I meant what I said about Al.
真的很遗憾
I'm truly sorry.
他独一无二
He was one of a kind.
嗯
Yeah.
对不起  埃尔
I'm sorry, Al.
真的对不起
So sorry...